

Amirhossein Najafizadeh

SRE / DevOps Engineer

I'm a full time Junior Backend developer with 4 years of experience in computers and networks. I always enjoy learn new things and experience new situations. Priority of my job is so high for me and I always put all of my effort to do the best I can.

Personal Information

Born: 2001

Military Service: Education Pardon

Marriage Statue: Single

Education: Computer Engineering Bachelor

at Amirkabir University of Tehran

Contact Me

Phone: +989155232106

Email: najafizadeh21@gmail.com

Github: amirhnajafiz

LinkedIn: <u>amirhossein.najafizadeh</u> **Website**: <u>amirhnajafiz.github.io</u>

Work Experiences



SRE / Backend Developer at Snapp!

Jan 2023 - Present

Working as SRE Engineer and Backend Developer in Snappline! team at Snapp!

Backend Developer at Snapp!

Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

Working as Software Engineer in Dispatching team at Snapp!

OS and Cloud Computing TA

Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

Teacher Assistant of Operating Systems and Cloud Computing courses at Amirkabir University of Tehran

Courses and Certificates



Backend internship at Snapp!

Learning Golang, Docker, Kubernetes, Micro-service, CI/CD, Openshift

3 Months

Laravel Bootcamp at MaktabSharif

Learning PHP, Laravel, MVC, MySQL, Redis, MongoDB, NginX

6 Months

Kubernetes at KodeKloud

Learning Containers, Docker, Swarm, Kubernetes, Kubernetes Administration, Helm Charts, Istio

72 Hours

Skills



Software

- Golang
- Python
- JavaScript
- SQL, MySQL
- MongoDB
- Redis, Dragonfly
- S3
- RTC, WebRTC
- SSE
- AuthO
- NATS, JetStream
- Kafka
- RabbitMQ
- Rest API
- Micro-Service
- Monolithic
- MVC, MVP
- Scrum, XP

SRE

- Git
- Shell Script
- Linux
- Gitlab CI
- Gitlab Runner
- Github Actions
- Prometheus
- Victoria Metrics
- Gerafana
- Kibana
- Blackbox Exporter
- Harbor
- ArgoCD

DevOps

- VM
- Containers
- Docker
- Swarm
- Kubernetes
- KubernetesOperators
- Helm Charts
- OpenShift
- Istio
- QEMU
- OpenStack
- NginX

Networking

- HTTP/HTTPS Proxy, Tunneling
- Firewall
- TCP/IP, OSI
- DNS, DHCP SSH, TLS

Projects



Stallion Message Broker

Implementing my own message broker with Golang.

<u>View Organization</u>

NginX Operator

Creating a kubernetes operator for deploying NginX application based on ConfigMap changes.

View Repository

Charlie

Executing python scripts on Kubernetes as fast as possible. <u>View Repository</u>

MQTT BlackBox Exporter

Blackbox exporter for RabbitMQ cluster.

<u>View Repository</u>

Prometheus Exporter

Implementing a prometheus metrics exporter.

<u>View Repository</u>